// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " 4 * 1 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " 2 * 3 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 4 * 4 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "12",
      "14",
      "16",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " 3 * 5 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "20",
      "15",
      "13",
      "12"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " 3 * 10 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "30",
    options: [
      "10",
      "12",
      "13",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " 0 * 1 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " 6 * 4 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "24",
    options: [
      "21",
      "22",
      "24",
      "26"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: " 7 * 6 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "42",
    options: [
      "42",
      "45",
      "49",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: " 8 * 8 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "64",
    options: [
      "60",
      "64",
      "66",
      "62"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 9 * 9 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "81",
    options: [
      "18",
      "88",
      "17",
      "81"
    ]
  }
  
];
